<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ParkingSpot</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <!-- String for Main menu -->
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>

    <!-- Strings for recycler view -->
    <string name="chapterstr1">Mr. and Mrs. Dursley, of number four, Privet Drive, were proud to say that they were perfectly normal, thank you very much.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr2"> They were the last people youd expect to be involved in anything strange or mysterious because they just didnt hold with such nonsense.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr3">Mr. Dursley was the director of a firm called Grunnings, which made drills.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr4">He was a big, beefy man with hardly any neck, although he did have a very large mustache.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr5">Mrs. Dursley was thin and blonde and had nearly twice the usual amount of neck, which came in very useful as she spent so much of her time craning over garden fences, spying on the neighbors.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr6">The Dursleys had a small son called Dudley and in their opinion there was no finer boy anywhere.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr7">The Dursleys had everything they wanted, but they also had a secret, and their greatest fear was that somebody would discover it.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr8">They didnt think they could bear it if anyone found out about the Potters.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr9">Mrs. Potter was Mrs. Dursleys sister, but they hadnt met for several years; in fact, Mrs. Dursley pretended she didnt have a sister, because her sister and her good-for-nothing husband were as unDursleyish as it was possible to be.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr10">The Dursleys shuddered to think what the neighbors would say if the Potters arrived in the street.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr11">The Dursleys knew that the Potters had a small son, too, but they had never even seen him.</string>
    <string name="chapterstr12">This boy was another good reason for keeping the Potters away; they didnt want Duddley mixing with a child like that.. </string>

</resources>